Well, you made it.
恭喜大家做到了
Made what?
做到什么了？
Made it to the,
在我看来
in my opinion, best part of the term.
做到终于可以学习这学期的最精彩部分了
This is where it all comes to life.
所有知识将变得有趣起来
That's part of the term but they've already learned so much good stuff.
这学期最精彩的部分？但是他们已经学了很多精彩的知识
They've already created their own trading strategies
他们已经创建了自己的交易策略
and they're already developing strong market intuition.
对市场有了比较强烈的直觉
They have an idea for how quant research works and
知道量化研究的工作流程
how production quality, trading strategies work.
产品质量和交易策略的原理
They know about markets, volatility,
学习了市场 波动率
outliers, indices and ETFs.
离群值 指数和 ETF
They even know how to create optimal diverse portfolios,
甚至知道如何创建最优分散投资组合
trading off volatility or risk with return.
权衡波动率或风险与收益率
Yeah, that's true, and learning all of those things help bring them to
没错 掌握所有这些知识
the point where they can fully appreciate what they're doing now.
有助于大家完全明白这节课要学的知识
But now we're going to put it all together and they're
但现在我们会将所有这些知识组合到一起
finally going to see the whole process end to end,
最终会看到一个端到端的完整流程
from an initial hypothesis,
从最初的假设
maybe from an academic paper,
例如从学术论文中
we'll see a few real life examples to quantify non-hypothesis,
了解几个真实的例子并量化为假设
to combining information of many types from many sources
将很多来源的各种信息组合到一起
about drivers of mean returns and drivers of volatility into a single model.
例如关于均值收益率和波动率的信息 并创建一个模型
Then using optimization tools we've already introduced,
然后使用我们已经介绍过的优化工具
to turn that into a production quality,
将该模型变成一个符合生产质量
theoretical tradable portfolio ready for a barrage of further testing.
从理论上来说可以交易的投资组合 并能够接受各种检验
Well you certainly have my attention.
听起来很吸引人
Is this how real quants do it?
这些是量化分析师的实际工作流程吗？
Absolutely. This is how real quants do it.
对这些就是量化分析师的实际工作流程
Well, that's exciting.
很有趣
Wait, when you mentioned ways to quantify a hypothesis,
你刚刚说的量化假设的方式
are you referring to the alphas that we discussed
是指我们在讨论量化工作流程时
back when we were talking about the quantum workflow?
提到的 alpha 吗？
Yep. That's exactly right.
是的完全正确
We're going to talk about alphas in great detail.
我们将详细讲解 alpha
Okay. So, students are going to hear about all of these in these lessons.
Ok学员将在后面的课程中学习这些知识
But will they get hands-on experience to?
但是他们有实践机会吗？
Absolutely, your final project for this term,
有的 这学期的最终实战项目
will give you a chance to demonstrate your understanding of this whole process.
将使学员有机会展示对整个流程的理解
Frankly, I'm excited that you'll have a chance to learn about these fundamental tools.
很激动大家有机会学习这些基础工具
I actually don't know of anywhere else where you can find
说实话 在我看来 其他教学机构根本不会提供
this kind of practical instruction in these methods.
这些实用的教学方法
In this lesson, you'll get an inside view of how practitioners translate
在这节课 你将深入了解从业人员
ideas into alpha models and then implement those alpha models in code.
如何将想法变成 alpha 模型 然后在代码中实现这些 alpha 模型
Personally, I'm also very excited that Jonathan has designed this module to give you
我也很激动 Jonathan 设计了这个模块
a real practitioner's perspective of how to combine
从从业人员的角度讲解了如何根据数据
data with an idea and implement it in code.
将想法变成模型并实现到代码中
Yep, this is awesome.
是的 太棒了
We're all super excited that you've reached
你终于跟着我们学到了这个阶段
this point in your journey with us and we hope you are too.
我们感到很激动
Without further ado, let's get started.
言归正传 我们开始吧